digitalstormonline.com 2007-12-19

# Digital Stom Privacy Policy

We believe your right to privacy and data security is our high priority.

Digital Storm is a proud member of the Better Business Bureau serving San Jose, California. This statement discloses the privacy guidelines for the entire Digital Storm website.

For more information about our privacy or information usage guidelines, please contact Digital Storm at sales@digitalstormonline.com. and put "Privacy" in the subject line.

Digital Storm only asks for specific types of personal information which will allow us to fully process your order(s).

On the Digital Storm web site, you will be asked to provide information that will allow us to process your order.

Digital Storm requests information from you when you place an order or check the status on your computer system.

Digital Storm may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, customer preference information, customer number, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to place an order with Digital Storm. If Digital Storm ever asks for significantly different information you will be informed.

Digital Storm only uses your personal information for specific purposes

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Digital Storm. Representatives of Digital Storm who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Digital Storm.

Digital Storm will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent.

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent.

Digital Storm wants to help you keep your personal information secure.

You can request the individual information that Digital Storm has collected about you via the Internet at sales@digitalstormonline.com or dial 1-866-81-STORM ext. 12.
